IntelliJ IDEA allows you to completely
IntelliJ IDEA可以让您完全
customize how your projects code is
自定义项目代码的方式
formatted down to the very last
格式化到最后
whitespace parentheses and brace what's
空格括号和括号是什么
more is you can add those formatting or
您还可以添加这些格式或
code style settings to version control
代码样式设置以进行版本控制
and they'll be immediately available to
他们将立即提供给
all IntelliJ IDEA users who pull from
从中退出的所有IntelliJ IDEA用户
your repository let's briefly take a
您的存储库让我们简要地介绍一下
look at a few ways you can work with
看看可以使用的几种方法
code Styles now first there are two
代码样式现在首先有两个
schemes for storing your code style
存储代码样式的方案
settings one is a project scheme that
设置之一是一个项目计划
will apply to this current project only
仅适用于当前项目
you can also manage your code styles at
您还可以在以下位置管理代码样式
a default or global level which will
默认级别或全局级别
apply to all projects on initialisation
应用于所有初始化项目
now there are a number of options for
现在有很多选择
configuring the line separators margin
配置行分隔符边距
lengths and default indentations that
长度和默认缩进
you'll use her basic code editing and
您将使用她的基本代码编辑功能，
you can further configure each of these
您可以进一步配置每个
in-depth in dozens of languages in many
深入介绍多种语言
many different contexts inside your code
您代码中的许多不同上下文
you can go in and edit one of the
您可以进入其中一个
provided schemes or manage your own and
提供的方案或管理您自己的方案和
import one from an external source here
从此处从外部来源导入一个
you can see IntelliJ IDEA is detected I
您可以看到检测到IntelliJ IDEA
have an eclipse installation and I can
有一个日食安装，我可以
import that directly if you're satisfied
如果您满意，则直接导入
with your existing code style but you
使用您现有的代码样式，但是您
frequently work with code that uses a
经常与使用
different convention then IntelliJ IDEA
与IntelliJ IDEA不同的约定
can detect and use the existing file
可以检测和使用现有文件
indents for editing and you can see here
缩进进行编辑，您可以在此处看到
that I've set the tab size to be four
我将标签页的大小设置为四个
and the indent length to before as well
以及缩进长度到之前
and in this project you can see that the
在这个项目中，您可以看到
defaults tab length is set to two spaces
默认选项卡长度设置为两个空格
with this feature enabled whenever I add
每当我添加时启用此功能
a new line IntelliJ IDEA will detect and
一行新的IntelliJ IDEA将检测并
apply the surrounding code style even if
应用周围的代码样式，即使
it conflicts with the code style in your
它与您的代码样式冲突
settings however if you'd like to
设置，但是如果您想
enforce IntelliJ IDEA code style you can
可以执行IntelliJ IDEA代码样式
open code and select reformat code or
打开代码并选择重新格式化代码或
press control alt pal you can also
按控制alt pal，您也可以
perform this action on a directory or
在目录上执行此操作或
project wide level by selecting in the
通过选择
project view and performing the same
项目视图并执行相同的操作
action from here you can choose to
您可以从此处选择操作
enable only reformatting that text
仅启用重新格式化该文本
has changed since the last VCS check-in
自上次VCS签入以来已更改
another way to quickly fix the
快速修复问题的另一种方法
indentation her particular file or set
缩进她的特定文件或集合
of lines without having to reformat your
行而不必重新格式化
code is by selecting the lines that
代码是通过选择
you'd like to reformat and by pressing
您想重新格式化并按
ctrl or command alt I which will quickly
Ctrl或Command Alt I，它将很快
fix the indents for the current
修复当前缩进
selection
选择